

#### **PROFILE**

Skilled UX/UI Designer and certified Scrum Product Owner with 14+ years of experience in designing and managing IT products — mobile applications, marketplaces, Saas, fin-tech apps. Offering strong communication skills and the ability to collaborate as a motivated and dedicated professional.

## **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY**

### Product Designer, RazumAI

OCTOBER 2022 - PRESENT

Creating concepts, visual mockups, specifications, final designs. Representing designs to the product team.

## Lead UX Designer, Luxoft

OCTOBER 2021 - SEPTEMBER 2022

Usability testing, analysis, user interviews. Making Design System in Figma. Conducting Heuristic Evaluation.

# Lead UX/UI Designer, Scrum Product Owner, Feel The Fun Company

DECEMBER 2019 — SEPTEMBER 2021

Created storyboards and personas as per users, and incorporated them into design decisions, resulting in an improved design creation. Data analysis using A/B testing.

### Lead UX/UI Designer, Scrum Product Owner, Olimp

AUGUST 2018 — SEPTEMBER 2019

UX/UI Design of Web, iOS, Android, PWA applications and game interfaces. Managing a team of developers, QA engineers, etc. Implementation of Agile and Scrum methodologies. Running hackathons and presentations for stakeholders. Conducting usability testing.

## Lead UX/UI Designer, Scrum Product Owner, MST24

FEBRUARY 2012 - AUGUST 2018

Created interaction strategies, developing navigation and flow, designing wireframes and interactive prototypes, organizing content, and advocating for the needs and goals of real users. Conceive, plan and lead the development of high-end, useful digital product. Managing a development team.

## **EDUCATION**

# Master of Visual Arts, Sholokhov Moscow State University for Humanities

MAY 2014

Diploma with mention of excellence.

#### **COURSES**

**Human-Computer Interaction, Stanford University** 

Professional Scrum Product Owner at Unusual Concepts (Scrum.org)

#### Contact

Remote

+7 (916) 180-6167 alex.mikhailov@gmail.com

### **Key Skills**

- · Usability Testing
- Heuristic Evaluation
- Atomic Design Methodology
- Scrum and Agile
- Jira Product Backlog management
- Impact Mapping
- English C1 Advanced

#### **Toolkit**

- Figma
- Sketch
- Adobe Creative Suite
- IIRA
- Zeplin
- InVision
- Miro

#### Certification

Professional Scrum Product Owner www.scrum.org/user/256382

